Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
Edmund B. Chaffee Papers
- Correspondence
  - 1931
    - Unemployed Union of New York, The (Box 29)
    - Uniformed Fireman’s Association (Box 29)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 29)
    - United Neighborhood Houses (Box 29)
    - Unit - Univ (Box 29)
    - VanD - Vang (Box 29)
    - Vedder, Beverly (Box 29)
    - Vic - Vik (Box 29)
    - W E V D (Box 29)
    - Wagner, Helen (Box 29)
    - Wagner, Robert A., Senator (Box 29)
    - Waid, D. E. (Box 29)
    - Walker, James J., Mayor of New York City (Box 29)
    - Wam - Wan (Box 29)
    - War Registers’ League, 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Was - Wat (Box 29)
    - Wei - Welf (Box 29)
    - Well - Wes (Box 29)
    - Whe - Whi (Box 29)
    - Wie - Win (Box 29)
    - Wom - Wor (Box 29)
    - Wright, C. M. – Thomas (Box 29)
    - Wylie, D. W. (Box 29)
    - Y.M.C.A., 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Y.W.C.A., 6 folders (Box 29)
    - Yager, Herman (Box 29)
    - Young, Reverend Bradford (Box 29)
    - Zollikoffer, Mrs. O. F. (Box 29)
    - Unidentified (Box 29)
    - To and From Others (Box 29)
  - 1932
    - Add - Ade (Box 30)
    - Affiliated Schools for Workers, The (Box 30)
    - Ali - All (Box 30)
    - American A - F (Box 30)
    - American Federation of Labor, The (Box 30)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 30)
    - American League to Abolish Capital Punishment (Box 30)
    - American League for India’s Freedom (Box 30)
    - American M - P (Box 30)
    - American Socia - Socie (Box 30)
    - Anderson, Dr. B. (Box 30)
    - Anderson, Nelson (Box 30)
    - Anderson, Sherwood (Box 30)
    - Andrews, George Reed (Box 30)
    - Arnold Constable and Company (Box 30)
    - Association for Improving the Poor (Box 30)
    - Atlantic Monthly, The (Box 30)
    - Ayers, Benjamin R. (Box 30)
    - Bai - Bel (Box 30)
    - Barlow, Reverend John (Box 30)
    - Barnes, Harry Elmer (Box 30)
    - Barnes, R. - Barr (Box 30)
    - Beck, G. F. (Box 30)
    - Becker - Ber (Box 30)
    - Bird - Brim (Box 30)
    - Blanshard, Paul (Box 30)
    - Blood - Bloom (Box 30)
    - Boc - Bow (Box 30)
    - Bra - Bron (Box 30)
    - Brooklyn (Box 30)
    - Brookw - Brot (Box 30)
    - Brown M. - O. M. (Box 30)
    - Brown, Thatcher M., Chairman, Yale Dramatic Association (Box 30)
    - Brownlee, M. R. (Box 30)
    - Buc - But (Box 30)
    - Cai - Car (Box 30)
    - Cente - Central S. (Box 30)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Chaffee, H. Elliott (Box 30)
    - Chap - Chas (Box 30)
    - Chi Alpha (Box 30)
    - Christian Century, The, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Christian U - Chug (Box 30)
    - Church League for Industrial Democracy (Box 30)
    - Church Loyalty and Home Visitation Evangelism Crusade (Box 30)
    - Churchman, The (Box 30)
    - Cit - Civ (Box 30)
    - Cla - Cli (Box 30)
    - Coa - Coe (Box 30)
    - Coffin, Henry S. (Box 30)
    - Cog - Col (Box 30)
    - Com - Cong (Box 30)
    - Cons - Cont (Box 30)
    - Correlated Graphic Industries (Box 30)
    - Corsi, Edward, Commissioner of Immigration, N. Y. District, U.S. Department of Labor (Box 30)
    - Cox, Eugene A. (Box 30)
    - Cul - Cur (Box 30)
    - Dai - Davis, H. M. (Box 30)
    - Davis, Jerome (Box 30)
    - Daviso - Day (Box 30)
    - Dimondstein, Boris (Box 30)
    - Drysdale, Reverend Euphemia (Box 30)
    - Dub - Duf (Box 30)
    - Durant, Will (Box 30)
    - Dwight, Dr. Kirby (Box 30)
    - Eastern Clergy Bureau (Box 30)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 30)
    - Eld - Els (Box 30)
    - Emergency Shelter, The (Box 30)
    - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee (Box 30)
    - Emergency Work Bureau (Box 31)
    - Emmett, Ruth (Box 31)
    - Equita - Equiti (Box 31)
    - Erie Inter-Church Federation (Box 31)
    - Fai - Fay (Box 31)
    - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Federation for the Support of Jewish Philanthropic Societies (Box 31)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies Fellowship of Faiths (Box 31)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Fellowship of Socialist Christians (Box 31)
    - Fie - Fit (Box 31)
    - Flanagan, Sue (Box 31)
    - Fle - Flo (Box 31)
    - Fog - For (Box 31)
    - Fosdick, Harry Emerson (Box 31)
    - Foulkes, William Robertson (Box 31)
    - Fra - Friends F. (Box 31)
    - Friends Seminary (Box 31)
    - Gardner, John, Garden City Community Church (Box 31)
    - Geske, Walter A. (Box 31)
    - Gillespie, James P. (Box 31)
    - Gleason, John (Box 31)
    - Gold - Golds (Box 31)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 31)
    - Goul - Gour (Box 31)
    - Gram - Gran (Box 31)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches (Box 31)
    - Gree - Gro (Box 31)
    - Gu (Box 31)
    - Hag - Hal (Box 31)
    - Harkness, Edward J. (Box 31)
    - Harp - Haw (Box 31)
    - Hel - Hes (Box 31)
    - Hil - Hit (Box 31)
    - Hod - Holme (Box 31)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 31)
    - Hom - How (Box 31)
    - Hum - Hus (Box 31)
    - Hyslop House (Box 31)
    - Ickes, Harold L. (Box 31)
    - Imes, William Lloyd, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Imrie, Gordon (Box 31)
    - Ind - Inn (Box 31)
    - Ins - Int (Box 31)
    - Isaacs, Martin (Box 31)
    - Italian Chamber of Labor (Box 31)
    - Jac - Jap (Box 31)
    - Jel - Jew (Box 31)
    - Johnson, Albert, Congressman (Box 31)
    - Joi - Jou (Box 31)
    - Kaufman, Eleanor (Box 31)
    - Kel - Ken (Box 31)
    - Kin - Kip (Box 31)
    - Kli - Klo (Box 31)
    - Knight, Walter David (Box 31)
    - Kroll, Reverend William (Box 31)
    - L. T. Building Corporation (Box 31)
    - Labor - Labor R (Box 31)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Services, Responses (Box 32)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 32)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices, Responses, Arrangements for, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Contributions to Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies and Equipment (Box 32)
      - Programs and Activities, 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Solicitations for Labor Temple Business (Box 32)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorello H., Congressman (Box 32)
    - Lai - Law (Box 32)
    - Leach, Henry Goddard (Box 32)
    - League for Independent Political Action (Box 32)
    - League for Industrial Democracy (Box 32)
    - League for Mutual Aid, The (Box 32)
    - League of Nations Association, Inc. (Box 32)
    - Leav - Leip (Box 32)
    - Lib - Liv (Box 32)
    - Lob - Low (Box 32)
    - Lutheran Welfare Council (Box 32)
    - Lyons, Alexander (Box 32)
    - Mac - Mari (Box 32)
    - Marti - Marts (Box 32)
    - Mas - May (Box 32)
    - McA - McN (Box 32)
    - Mei - Meth (Box 32)
    - Metr - Mez (Box 32)
    - Mil - Miz (Box 32)
    - Mod - Mol (Box 32)
    - Mosher, William E. (Box 32)
    - Mul - Mur (Box 32)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 32)
    - Nash, Mrs. John B. (Box 32)
    - N.A.A.C.P. (Box 32)
    - Nation, The (Box 32)
    - National Catholic Welfare Conference (Box 32)
    - National Committee to Aid Striking Miners (Box 32)
    - National Committee of... (Box 32)
    - National Conference Council (Box 32)
    - National G - R (Box 32)
    - Nea - New W (Box 32)
    - New York A - New York City C (Box 32)
    - New York City Mission Society, Jelliffe, W. R., Executive Vice-President (Box 32)
    - New York City Municipal Listings (Box 32)
    - New York Committee of One Thousand (Box 32)
    - New York Conference for Unemployment (Box 32)
    - New York F - H (Box 32)
    - New York I - W (Box 32)
    - Nieubuhr, Reinhold (Box 32)
    - Noble, Harry W. (Box 32)
    - Nolting, Edward L. (Box 32)
    - Now - Noy (Box 32)
    - Nye, Gerald P., Senator (Box 32)
    - O'Hare, F. P. (Box 33)
    - Open Forum Speakers' Bureau (Box 33)
    - Opi - Ot (Box 33)
    - Outlook (and Independent) (Box 33)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 33)
    - Pai - Patt (Box 33)
    - Pek - Per (Box 33)
    - Pic - Pit (Box 33)
    - Poo - Pow (Box 33)
    - Presbyterian Banner (Box 33)
    - Presbyterian Board of Christian Education (Box 33)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.
      - Board of Christian Education (Box 33)
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 33)
      - Board of National Missions, 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Board of Pensions (Box 33)
      - Office of General Assembly (Box 33)
      - The Presbyterian Magazine (Box 33)
      - Synod of New York (Box 33)
    - Presbyterian Ministers Fund (Box 33)
    - Presbyterian Union of New York City (Box 33)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Bartlett, M., Stated Clerk (Box 33)
      - Church Extension Commission
        - Merle-Smith, Van S., Treasurer (Box 33)
        - Savage, T. F., Secretary, 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 33)
      - Mendenhall, H. G., Stated Clerk (Box 33)
      - Social Service Committee, 3 folders (Box 33)
      - Youth of New York (Box 33)
    - Protestant Charities Commission (Box 33)
    - Protestant Social Service, Inc. (Box 33)
    - Public Committee on Power Utilities and Labor (Box 33)
    - Quill Club, The (Box 33)
    - Raf - Rat (Box 33)
    - Rebel Poet, The (Box 33)
    - Reconciliation Trips, 3 folders (Box 33)
    - Ref - Rel (Box 33)
    - Richards, Edward C. M. (Box 33)
    - Richards, George H., 5 folders (Box 33)
    - Richma - Richmo (Box 33)
    - Rob - Rot (Box 33)
    - Rus - Rux (Box 33)
    - Rybicki, Edward C. (Box 33)
    - Sal - Sau (Box 33)
    - Save the Children Fund (Box 33)
    - Sche - Scoo (Box 33)
    - Scott, Philip Gordon (Box 33)
    - Sea - Set (Box 33)
    - Sha - Shi (Box 33)
    - Sib - Sim (Box 33)
    - Slater, Thomas (Box 34)
    - Sloan, Alfred P., Jr. (Box 34)
    - Smith... (Box 34)
    - Sockman, Ralph W. (Box 34)
    - Soci - Sou (Box 34)
    - Sparks, John B. (Box 34)
    - Speers, Thomas Guthrie (Box 34)
    - Spoerri, Raymond (Box 34)
    - Star - Stau (Box 34)
    - Stelzle, Charles (Box 34)
    - Stew - Stu (Box 34)
    - Subke, Walter C. (Box 34)
    - Swift, Arthur (Box 34)
    - Syroka, Mary (Box 34)
    - Tamblyn and Brown (Box 34)
    - Tea - Tee (Box 34)
    - Theta (Box 34)
    - Thomas A - F (Box 34)
    - Thomas, Norman (Box 34)
    - Threefold Commonwealth League (Box 34)
    - Til - Tim (Box 34)
    - Tresca, Carlo (Box 34)
    - Und - Unif (Box 34)
    - Union Settlement (Box 34)
    - Union Theological Seminary (Box 34)
    - Unitar - United N (Box 34)
    - United P - Univ (Box 34)
    - Van Dyke, Tertius (Box 34)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Box 34)
    - Vondermuhhl, Kate (Box 34)
    - W.E.V.D. (Box 34)
    - Walk - Walt (Box 34)
    - Ward - Warren (Box 34)
    - War Resisters League, 3 folders (Box 34)
    - Was - Watts (Box 34)
    - Web - Wel (Box 34)
    - White - Whiteh (Box 34)
    - Wil - Win (Box 34)
    - Wise, Stephen S. (Box 34)
    - Wolfson, John (Box 34)
    - Woll, Matthew (Box 34)
    - Wom - World C. (Box 34)
    - World Tomorrow (Box 34)
    - World's, S - Worn (Box 34)
    - Wright (Box 34)
    - Wyer, Samuel S. (Box 34)
    - Yarrow, Clarence H. (Box 34)
    - Y.M.C.A., 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Young People's Peace Conference (Box 34)
    - Y.W.C.A., 4 folders (Box 34)
    - Zito, George (Box 34)
    - Unidentified (Box 34)
    - To and From Others (Box 34)
  - 1933
    - Ada - Adi (Box 34)
    - Affiliated Schools for Workers (Box 34)
    - Age - Agn (Box 34)
    - Ahrend, D. H. Company (Box 34)
    - Akin, Miss Mildred (Box 34)
    - Ale - All (Box 34)
    - Ama - American Ch (Box 34)
    - American Co. - American League Against (Box 34)
    - American League for - American Legion (Box 34)
    - American P - Y (Box 34)
    - Ammon, Bertha A. (Box 34)
    - And - Ant (Box 34)
    - Are - Art (Box 34)
    - Ash - Ass (Box 34)
    - Austin... (Box 34)
    - Axelbank, H. (Box 34)
    - Ayers, Benjamin K. (Box 34)
    - Bab - Bai (Box 34)
    - Bak - Bau (Box 34)
    - Bea - Beck C. (Box 35)
    - Beck, G. F. (Box 35)
    - Bel - Berk (Box 35)
    - Berman, Max (Box 35)
    - Berte, Mrs. Jean (Box 35)
    - Bib - Bir (Box 35)
    - Blac - Blanshard B. (Box 35)
    - Blanshard, Paul (Box 35)
    - Bloch, Joshua (Box 35)
    - Bon - Bow (Box 35)
    - Bra - Brooks (Box 35)
    - Brookw - Brow (Box 35)
    - Bul - But (Box 35)
    - Cam - Car (Box 35)
    - Central R - T (Box 35)
    - Chadborne, Mrs. A. H. (Box 35)
    - Chaffee, Family of, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - Chaffee, H. A. (Box 35)
    - Christian Advo (Box 35)
    - Christian Century, The, 3 folders (Box 35)
    - Christian S - Chu (Box 35)
    - Citi - City (Box 35)
    - Clark - Clarke (Box 35)
    - Cle - Clu (Box 35)
    - Codina, Cicero (Box 35)
    - Coffin, Henry Sloane (Box 35)
    - Coh - Colle (Box 35)
    - Colli - Colt (Box 35)
    - Columbia University (Box 35)
    - Coma - Committee on H (Box 35)
    - Committee on M - Communist (Box 35)
    - Communit - Comp (Box 35)
    - Conference for Progressive Labor Action (Box 35)
    - Conference of - Conference On (Box 35)
    - Cong - Cont (Box 35)
    - Coo - Corb (Box 35)
    - Correlated Graphic Enterprises (Box 35)
    - Cory, Reverend David (Box 35)
    - Crai - Craw (Box 35)
    - Cuo - Cur (Box 35)
    - Dal - Dan (Box 35)
    - David - Davis (Box 35)
    - Davison - Day (Box 35)
    - Den - DeR (Box 35)
    - Die - Din (Box 35)
    - Dod - Dow (Box 35)
    - Dressmakers' Union Local 22 (Box 35)
    - Duff, George M. (Box 35)
    - Dwight, Margarethe (Box 35)
    - East S - Easter (Box 35)
    - Eddy, Sherwood (Box 35)
    - Edwards, Deane (Box 35)
    - Eggeling Bindery (Box 35)
    - Elliot... (Box 35)
    - Emergency C - S (Box 35)
    - Emergency Work Bureau (Box 35)
    - Emergency Unemployment Relief Committee (Box 35)
    - Epworth League, New York District (Box 35)
    - Eva - Eve (Box 35)
    - Fai - Far (Box 35)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America January-March (Box 35)
    - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America April-December, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - Federation O - S (Box 36)
    - Fei - Fellowship of Faiths (Box 36)
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Fellowship of S - Fey (Box 36)
    - Fif - Fit (Box 36)
    - Flag - Flanagan (Box 36)
    - Flanagan, Sue (Box 36)
    - Flanagan, W. - Fly (Box 36)
    - Foo - Ford (Box 36)
    - Foreign A - P (Box 36)
    - Fosdick, Harry E. (Box 36)
    - Foster, Marjorie (Box 36)
    - Fra - Fren (Box 36)
    - Fric - Fried (Box 36)
    - Friends Seminary, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Frost, Dr. Henry D. (Box 36)
    - Fulcomer, Reverend W. N. (Box 36)
    - Gal - Gat (Box 36)
    - Ged - Ger (Box 36)
    - Gif - Gip (Box 36)
    - Gol - Goo (Box 36)
    - Gordon, Dugald (Box 36)
    - Gordon, Wendell Chaffee (Box 36)
    - Gor - Gos (Box 36)
    - Gratton, Reverend John (Box 36)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Gree - Gro (Box 36)
    - Gua - Gut (Box 36)
    - Hal - Harc (Box 36)
    - Harkness, Edward S. (Box 36)
    - Harris, Helen M. (Box 36)
    - Hartford Seminary Foundation, Hartford Theological Seminary (Box 36)
    - Hartl - Hay (Box 36)
    - Hea - Hes (Box 36)
    - Hig - Hin (Box 36)
    - Hoa - Holl (Box 36)
    - Holmes, John Haynes, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Holmes, Richard S. (Box 36)
    - Holt - Hor (Box 36)
    - Hou - How (Box 36)
    - Hud - Hun (Box 36)
    - Hymn Society, The (Box 36)
    - Imes, W. L., 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Inne - Innes (Box 36)
    - Institute of F - R (Box 36)
    - International C - L (Box 36)
    - International Relief Association (Box 36)
    - Isaacs, Martin (Box 36)
    - Jac - Jap (Box 36)
    - Jacquith, Harold C. (Box 36)
    - Jen - Jew (Box 36)
    - Joint Peace Committee of New York Quakers (Box 37)
    - Jones, John Paul (Box 37)
    - Jones, Mary - Robert (Box 37)
    - Kahwaii, Assad (Box 37)
    - Kee - Kes (Box 37)
    - Kistler, Reverend Raymond (Box 37)
    - Kling, Phina (Box 37)
    - Knic - Knig (Box 37)
    - Kroll, Reverend William (Box 37)
    - Kuh - Kun (Box 37)
    - La - Labor Temple, 243 E. 84th St. (Box 37)
    - Labor Temple
      - Affirmations, Notices of Church Service, Responses (Box 37)
      - Annual Reports, Statements, Audits (Box 37)
      - Budget, Allocation of Funds, Finances (Box 37)
      - Committee Meetings, Notices and Responses, Arrangements for (Box 37)
      - Contributions to, Appeals and Responses, Thank You Notes, 3 folders (Box 37)
      - Employment Inquiries and Recommendations, 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Maintenance and Repairs, Supplies and Equipment (Box 37)
      - Programs and Activities, 6 folders (Box 37)
      - Work Schedules and Instructions to Personnel, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Lackland, George S. (Box 37)
    - Laconia Savings Bank (Box 37)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorello, Mayor of New York City (Box 37)
    - Landman, J. H. (Box 37)
    - League for Independent Political Action (Box 37)
    - League for Industrial Democracy (Box 37)
    - League of Mothers’Clubs (Box 37)
    - Lehman, Herbert H., Governor of New York (Box 37)
    - Lev - Lew (Box 37)
    - Lic - Lis (Box 37)
    - Lloyd, George (Box 37)
    - LoP - Low (Box 37)
    - Lundeen, Ernest, Congressman (Box 37)
    - Lyons, Dr. Alexander (Box 37)
    - Macmillan Company, The (Box 37)
    - Mac - Mac P (Box 37)
    - Mad - Mar (Box 37)
    - Mas - Mat (Box 37)
    - Mc (Box 37)
    - Med - Mer (Box 37)
    - Methodist-Episcopal Church (Box 37)
    - Metropolitan L - S (Box 37)
    - Mil - Min (Box 37)
    - Mor - Mou (Box 37)
    - Murray, Helen G. (Box 37)
    - Muste, A. J. (Box 37)
    - Nation, The (Box 37)
    - National A - Conference of (Box 37)
    - National Cons - National Rec (Box 37)
    - National Religion and Labor Foundation (Box 37)
    - National U - National W (Box 37)
    - Nea - Nei (Box 37)
    - New E - W (Box 37)
    - New York A - B (Box 37)
    - New York C - New York City Mission Society (Box 38)
    - New York, City of (Official City Gov't Listings) (Box 38)
    - New York Civic - New York L (Box 38)
    - New York School of Social Work (Box 38)
    - New York Society for the Suppression of Vice (Box 38)
    - New York, State of (Official State Gov't Listings) (Box 38)
    - New York State P - New York Un (Box 38)
    - New York Ur - New York W (Box 38)
    - Nic - Nicolson (Box 38)
    - Nied - Nix (Box 38)
    - Nob - Noy (Box 38)
    - Nye, Gerald P., Senator (Box 38)
    - O'Brien, Dan (Box 38)
    - Ohio Unemployed League (Box 38)
    - Onondaga Club (Box 38)
    - Opinion (Box 38)
    - Order of K - S (Box 38)
    - Osborne, A - H (Box 38)
    - Other Economics League, The (Box 38)
    - Owen, Ruth Bryan, Congresswoman (Box 38)
    - Owners and Tenants Electric Company (Box 38)
    - Page, Kirby (Box 38)
    - Pai - Pal (Box 38)
    - Park - Part (Box 38)
    - Pat - Pay (Box 38)
    - Ped - Pet (Box 38)
    - Philbrook, Ralph A. (Box 38)
    - Pic - Pioneer P. (Box 38)
    - Pioneer Youth of America (Box 38)
    - Planten, W. R. J. (Box 38)
    - Pon - Pot (Box 38)
    - Presbyterian, The (Box 38)
    - Presbyterian Advance (Box 38)
    - Presbyterian Banner (Box 38)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.
      - Board of Foreign Missions (Box 38)
      - Board of National Missions, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Board of Pensions (Box 38)
      - General Council Office of General Assembly (Box 38)
      - Synod of New York, Social Service Committee (Box 38)
    - Presbyterian Headquarters (Box 38)
    - Presbyterian Union of New York City (Box 38)
    - Presbytery of Brooklyn Nassau Department of Christian Education (Box 38)
    - Presbytery of New York
      - Bartlett, M., Stated Clerk (Box 38)
      - Church Extension Committee
        - Savage, T. F., Executive Secretary, 2 folders (Box 38)
      - Committee on Evangelism, Committee on Pensions, Committee on Programs and Field Activities (Box 38)
      - Department of Christian Education (Box 38)
      - Social Service Committee, 3 folders (Box 38)
      - Youth of New York Presbytery (Box 38)
    - Press - Pro (Box 38)
    - Pu (Box 38)
    - Quill Club, The (Box 38)
    - Rad - Ram (Box 38)
    - Read, Reverend Ralph H. (Box 38)
    - Reconciliation Trips (Box 38)
    - Ree - Res (Box 38)
    - Richards, Edward C. M., 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Richards, George H., 4 folders (Box 39)
    - Riverdale Country School (Box 39)
    - Rob - Ros (Box 39)
    - Ross - Rou (Box 39)
    - Russell Sage College (Box 39)
    - Rybicki, Edward S. (Box 39)
    - Sac - Sanb (Box 39)
    - Sanger, Margaret (Box 39)
    - Save the Children Fund, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Saw - Say (Box 39)
    - Sche - Schwa (Box 39)
    - Schwimmer, Rosika (Box 39)
    - Scott, C - H (Box 39)
    - Scott, Howard (Box 39)
    - Scully, John H. (Box 39)
    - Searle, Robert Wyckoff (Box 39)
    - Set - Sev (Box 39)
    - Shan - Shau (Box 39)
    - Sib - Sie (Box 39)
    - Sinclair, Upton (Box 39)
    - Sma - Sni (Box 39)
    - Sol - Son (Box 39)
    - Spe - Spr (Box 39)
    - Sta - Stee (Box 39)
    - Stel - Stoc (Box 39)
    - Stone, Hannah M. (Box 39)
    - Stone, M. D. - Stra (Box 39)
    - Stro - Stu (Box 39)
    - Subke, Walter Carl (Box 39)
    - Syracuse University, Hendricks Chapel, William H. Powers, Dean (Box 39)
    - Tam - Tay (Box 39)
    - Terzani Defense Committee (Box 39)
    - The - Thu (Box 39)
    - Tim - Tip (Box 39)
    - Tobbit, Reverend R. Hilton (Box 39)
    - Tre - Tri (Box 39)
    - Tuttle, Charles (Box 39)
    - Twee - Twen (Box 39)
    - Underwood, Lorraine (Box 39)
    - Union of Churches of Christ (Box 39)
    - Union Theological Seminary, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - United - United States C (Box 39)
    - United States, Government Listings (Box 39)
    - Universa - Universi (Box 39)
    - Urstadt, Emily M. (Box 39)
    - Van Doren, Irita (Box 39)
    - Van Du - Vas (Box 39)
    - Vermont, State of (Box 39)
    - Vik - Vil (Box 39)
    - Voca - Voci (Box 39)
    - Wal - Warren (Box 39)
    - War Resisters League, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Wats - Watt (Box 39)
    - Webb - Webs (Box 39)
    - Wef - Wel (Box 39)
    - Wer - Wes (Box 39)
    - Whe - Whi (Box 39)
    - Wilb - Will (Box 39)
    - Woll, Matthew (Box 39)
    - Wom - Wood (Box 39)
    - Woos - Wor (Box 39)
    - Wright, Glen (Box 40)
    - Wye - Wyl (Box 40)
    - Yale University School of Divinity, Luther Weigle, Dean (Box 40)
    - Yergin, Howard V. (Box 40)
    - Y.M.C.A., 5 folders (Box 40)
    - Y.W.C.A., 5 folders (Box 40)
    - Za (Box 40)
    - Unidentified (Box 40)
    - To and From Others (Box 40)
  - 1934
    - Ada - Ade (Box 40)
    - Ailanthus Hall Association, Inc. (Box 40)
    - Affiliated Schools for Workers, The (Box 40)
    - Ald - All (Box 40)
    - Ambruster, Howard W. (Box 40)
    - American A - Ba (Box 40)
    - American Birth Control League, Inc. (Box 40)
    - American Christian Alliance (Box 40)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 40)
    - American Fa - American League Against (Box 40)
    - American League to A - American Pe (Box 40)
    - American Psy - Socia (Box 40)
    - American Society - Young (Box 40)
    - American Worker's Party (Box 40)
    - And - Ant (Box 40)
    - Apelian, Bedros (Box 40)
    - Association for University Teas (Box 40)
    - Atlins, John A. (Box 40)
    - Automobile Insurance Company of Hartford (Box 40)
    - Ayers, B. K. (Box 40)
    - Bahnsen, Roland (Box 40)
    - Bail - Bair (Box 40)
    - Baker, Newton D. (Box 40)
    - Ball, Lee H. (Box 40)
    - Barber, George G. (Box 40)
    - Barnes, Roswell P. (Box 40)
    - Bar - Bat (Box 40)
    - Ben - Ber (Box 40)
    - Berman, Max (Box 40)
    - Bid - Bis (Box 40)
    - Bla - Blu (Box 40)
    - Bonanno, John and Mary (Box 40)
    - Bon - Bow (Box 40)
    - Bra - Bre (Box 40)
    - Bronx Free Fellowship (Box 40)
    - Bronx - Brooklyn (Box 40)
    - Brooks, Rachel G. (Box 40)